All right, the results are in.
For the school's cultural festival this year,
our class will be serving up Russian roulette tokoyaki.
Score!
I dig it.
Saintsy, sis.
We only have two weeks to prepare,
so focus, find your strengths fast,
and be sure to work as a team.
Yes, ma'am!
Special request for the men of our class,
I ask that you handle the physical labor of the interior designs.
Yes, ma'am!
I'll open the doors a little early
so you can get in some work before homeroom.
You can also come in at lunch or after school.
If you stay beyond the window of time we're allowed,
you will cost our team precious points.
I guess we better play by the rules.
So if we can lose these points, can we gain them?
We're awarded one point per customer,
and our points determine our rank.
If we fail to follow the rules,
points will be subtracted from our total.
So you'll really have to use your hats
if you want to bring home the gold.
One, five, go!
I didn't realize they were ranking us.
That just means we have to come in first!
Everybody else is toast!
They can choke on our tokoyaki.
They're so motivated.
The joys of teaching.
Please, class, quiet down.
The festival is two days long,
and the main event on day two will be a beauty pageant.
Wait, really?
I didn't know our school did that.
I think of it as our yearly dose of glamour and charm.
It's always a highlight.
Whoever places first in the pageant wins special points
and could very well lead their glass to victory.
Hold up. Only first?
That's correct.
Brutal!
If it's victory that we're after,
Kitagawa's our girl.
For real?
Of course he's for real.
You're like a literal model.
Let's get you a pageant gown.
I want to see her dressed all pretty.
Do it, Maureen!
Um, before you decide,
the theme this year is drag.
So I'm afraid the ball gown idea won't work.
If you choose Kitagawa as your candidate,
she'll have to dress as a boy.
What?
I get to dress up as one of my faves at school?
I'm begging you guys, please let me compete in this.
I promise I won't let you down.
We already made it clear that you should compete for us.
Yes, but what if some other cutie wants in?
Hana-chan!
I just have to look like a guy, right?
Could I dress up as a character?
There's no rule against it.
Stop it!
What's your nerd brain cooking up now?
Let me ponder.
Do duds.
Gotta do Ray-sama from Prez Host.
Ray-sama from Prez Host!
Ray-sama?
You mean Mommy?
They all know Prez Host?
It must be popular.
I've never watched it.
The chicks go crazy for the live-action version.
Heck yeah!
My mom and sis would kill for the himbo harem.
The show rocks!
The dudes are smokin',
but the lead actress is the most popular
because she's stupidly talented.
Wow.
Nice.
I think Prez Host is Miko's greatest performance ever!
She just radiated cool!
I love the manga and the anime,
but I guess I gotta watch the drama, too.
So, which of Ray's outfits are you gonna cosplay?
Maybe the suit?
Totes the suit!
No, duh.
But as for the exact moment...
It's gotta be the bento scene
after she gets off work at the host club.
That part just hits the field so hard it hurts me!
That scene's too powerful!
You're also a Prez Host fan, Murakami?
Yeah, sure.
My sister's favorite idol
plays one of the hosts in the live-action.
She had it on, so I watched it with her.
That bento scene crushed my freaking soul!
It's so emo!
It should be illegal!
I'm with you!
If Marin cosplays the bento scene,
we'll win for sure!
Must be a touching story.
Well, have we officially decided
Kitagawa will be our candidate?
Kitagawa?
Yeah?
There are two key components
you'll need to focus on.
The first is the costume.
The second is putting on a performance
to charm the audience.
I need some deets.
You'll each put on a brief show,
with your goal being
to win the Student Council's hearts.
And keep in mind,
you'll be trying to charm members
of your own sex.
You'll need creativity, cuteness,
and all the charisma you can muster.
Cool!
We're gonna score a helipoint
with our god-tier takoyaki!
It's up to you
to kick this beauty pageant's butt!
This is my freaking forte!
Right?
Gojo!
Time to study up on Press Host!
Gojo?
What am I missing here?
Gojo makes all Marines cosplays.
Epic, huh?
Goose Fitz rule!
I didn't realize
they were all staring.
Gojo?
Yeah!
The other classes are dead meat!
Dead meat!
Hush, please calm down.
J Forsyye Photoshop
Garing in the inner
ére
You
can't
.
Midnight
Ima wa maada kusa-guri de ba-yo-te-mo
Hope te eka-ki-da-su ki-kai
Mena-i-ro-no a-shita ga yon-de-ru
Mi-chi-shiru-te-naku-ta-te-gu-an-da-ne-wa-ke-ah-te-ki-mi-ga-iru-i-tsu-da-te-ho-ra-wara-te-
High five!
Oh no! If I don't hurry, I'll be late for classroom duties!
Excuse me? Did something happen to you?
I'm fine. I've just been busy dealing with patrons. I haven't had any time to eat.
Well, I'm not going to stand here and let you starve.
I know it might not be to your taste, but you're welcome to have my lunch!
Uh, thank you.
I've gotta run! I'm sorry!
Hey! Come back!
You didn't bring lunch today, Koyomi? What's going on?
I had a surprisingly eventful morning.
You're going to need to fill me in.
It's Rei-sama! She's as beautiful as ever!
Who is she?
She's our student council president, Rei Kogami!
She's gorgeous, gets amazing grades, and excels in sports!
Not only is she perfect, but she's kind!
She's so awesome, she has an official fan club! Gosh!
You may have just transferred, but I'm shocked you didn't know.
She's so dignified, like a queen! What a beautiful person!
Koyomi?
Hello?
We need to get ready for PE, so we should probably head-
I'm on classroom duty!
Will the following please report to the student council office.
Koyomi Mishima of Class 1C.
I messed up already? But what did I do?
This isn't a great first impression.
You wanted to see me?
Koyomi.
Thank you for this morning.
I so appreciate your help.
Your bento was delicious.
Truth is, both my parents passed away.
My older brother works as a host to make ends meet.
I went by his job to drop something off.
They were desperate for more hosts, so they threw me in a wig and a suit.
Now I work there part time.
You saw me, so I thought you should know.
But I ask that you keep it between us.
She-she-she's unbelievable!
Not only is she the beloved student council president, Ray!
She's the number one employee at the Free Boat Rose Club!
The handsome Ray!
Ignore those other guys. Only look at me.
Forget about Ray. I'm right here.
Come sit on my lap, little kitten.
You're my girl now. Best not forget it.
The tension between you and I is undeniable.
Tell them who's your daddy.
How could a regular girl end up part of a host club love heptagon?
What in the world is going to happen to me next?
I'm fixed!
Amazing job at work today.
I made this if you're hungry.
Thanks so much.
Sweet of you to think of me.
A lot of other girls will put trendy spins on their bentos.
But your cooking is just so...
It's so dull, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I've seen them.
The super cute bentos you get from the girls in your fan club.
Koyami, what are you saying?
You're used to eating high quality food at fancy restaurants with your patrons.
Ray has to be nice to everyone she meets.
Being friendly is part of her job.
Just because she's kind to me doesn't mean I'm special to her.
I can't believe I was foolish enough to get the wrong idea.
Your bentos are classic.
They remind me of what my mother used to make.
It puts me at ease.
Between school and work, I'm always so tense, always on edge.
But once I finally clock out and get to spend time with her,
all my worries melt away.
We've gotten so close because you know that I'm a host.
But it's because I'm a host that you won't believe me.
No matter what I say, or how I feel.
Ray-sama?
I know, right?
It totally wrecks your heart.
Now do you understand why everyone falls for her?
Yeah.
Really makes me want Ray to find happiness.
Yeah, exactly!
I really appreciate the fact that Ray isn't just cool cause she's pretty,
but because she understands how women feel and supports them as well.
For sure!
She can be assertive at times, but she's never pushy.
Like, she never forces champagne onto anyone!
Also, isn't Ray's ace, Sumugi, just the absolute best?
Better tell Koyomi to watch out, cause this chick is stone cold.
Yeah, I agree!
To Koyomi, she's a romantic rival.
But then she turns around and sticks up for Koyomi when it counts!
That's enough!
So, you're attacking this sweet young girl to spite Ray.
If you truly hate Ray so much, climb the ranks as revenge instead.
To hell with that!
She had the audacity to lie about being a man so she could become the number one host!
All of Ray's patrons are perfectly aware that she's a woman.
And even so, they come to see her.
Ray does not show us lies.
She shows us dreams.
Dreams so beautiful that ideas like sex and gender cease to matter.
Ray's who we want.
Who we need in a world full of miserable men like the three of you.
If it means I can help Ray shine, I couldn't care less if I'm not the star.
In order to remain at Ray's side, I'll continue to be her ace.
That's my greatest satisfaction.
You could say Tokiko Sumugi is the manlier of the two at that speech of hers!
I couldn't agree more.
Okay, for this one, we're going to need to make a complete outfit like a three-piece suit.
For the makeup, I want to express an androgynous beauty.
We'll need to slim out your face a bit.
As well as thicken your eyebrows a touch without going overboard.
Finally, we'll make your eyes pop by using reserved colors.
Oakley doakley!
Also...
The rainbow rose.
A flower shop perhaps has one.
For sure.
It's just that depending on which shop you go to,
an actual rainbow rose could probably run you around a thousand yen apiece.
That much for one rose?
How about this?
We get an artificial rose for cheap and we spray paint it to be rainbow.
Oh! Sweet!
Also, isn't Rei like super tall?
We can use insoles and boost my height.
It's perfect!
And the fabric we used for Nihon's course, it would be amazeables!
It's got total number one host vibes, don't you think?
If she were a normal number one host, I would have considered using it.
It would totally pop, right?
Wait, what?
While it's an elegant fabric, that's for sure.
I don't think it's quite right for the number one host, Rei, you know?
I mean, sure.
Rei-sama stands out because of her looks, but in reality, she's pretty reserved.
She only became student council president and a host because she was asked to.
She didn't seek it out on her own.
So for the suit fabric, I don't think going flashy is quite the right direction.
Not here, at least.
So true, bestie!
Although the club owner does get on her case a lot about dressing more like a number one host,
so I definitely think embossing this shirt is the right way to go for this cosplay.
Looking at the designs from the series got me curious about how all of the suits look so slim fit.
At first I thought that was just how they were depicted in shoujo manga,
but they're trimmed differently from business suits.
It's supposed to make the wearer look cooler.
Whoa, is that true?
Your curves will be obvious though,
so it might be kind of difficult to replicate a straighter, manlier body type.
Ah, gotcha.
I promise I'll still do everything in my power to make it work.
But the thing is, your waist is pretty thin.
So there's a chance you wouldn't make a convincing guy.
Then again...
Of course.
I guess it makes sense.
With all the cosplays we've done together,
Gojo has all my measurements memorized.
That's... a little bit...
So what's your opinion on it?
Wait, what now?!
Oh yeah, we've so got this!
There's still two weeks till the cultural festival!
Oh...
Well, uh...
Hmm?
Since you're the one entering the beauty pageant,
you'll be able to spend all of your time working on your outfit.
Hmm...
But I'm on interior design duty and will likely be pretty busy.
Uh...
So if I can only work on this after interior design,
I'll have even less time than I did with Shizuku-tan!
Uh...
So this is gonna be rough, huh?
Hey...
Huh?
About the Rei cosplay...
I'll put it together myself, okay?
Alright...
Easy enough.
I'll just head out and grab all of this.
If you don't know what something is, just call me.
Also while you're there, talk to Mr. Usami.
He'll definitely be able to help you out.
Gotcha!
I'll draft up instructions on how to make the outfit,
but Kitagawa...
Will you really be okay?
Yeah!
It'll be no biggie!
I can absolutely pull this off,
so don't you worry about a thing!
I'm worrying...
Usually shopping is a ton of fun,
because it means I'm getting ready for another cosplay.
But...
Without Gojo around...
I'm freaking out!
I have to make sure I don't buy the wrong stuff!
I'm winning first place, so I've gotta work hard!
Worst case scenario...
I just work day one of the cultural festival,
and somehow make it to the beauty pageant on day two.
I'll need to do the interior design,
the instructions for the outfit, and...
It'll be okay, if I just believe I can do it.
Except...
I have to manage my time properly.
So that I don't end up burdening anybody else.
Okay...
Listen up!
Uh...
Gojo...
Is something wrong?
What are you doing here?
I...
Uh...
Thought I'd help with interior design.
Huh?
Really?
Dude, we got all that covered.
You need to make the pageant outfit, right?
Huh?
Bro, I'm the one who's confused right now.
Aren't you making Kitagawa's outfit?
That's what I thought, too.
Did I misremember?
I thought so, too.
Guess we were wrong.
He always makes our cosplays, though.
Yeah.
Oh, wait a sec!
Were you planning on doing both since Hana asked you guys to help out with the interior design?
Come on, man!
I mean, an extra pair of hands would be awesome,
but you're not some kind of superhuman.
Don't overdo it.
The strange man has a point.
None of us think making an outfit is easy.
You don't have time to spare.
Just leave it to us.
I can try to do both.
Seriously?
That's amazing!
You're the best!
Hey!
Gojo, be honest.
You know doing both would wear you out, right?
Just say so.
Yeah.
See?
So just leave it to us, okay, bro?
But you've actually got to speak up.
I mean, if you say it's fine, this guy will take it at face value,
cause he's stupid.
Ouch.
But he's right.
You just focus on the cosplay and we'll take care of everything here.
Let's all get first place together.
And then that leaves us who pretty much can't help anyone with any of it!
I know, right?
I feel like I would immediately screw up the sewing machine.
You're basically a god for even knowing how to work with sewing machines.
I mean, I could try helping with something else.
All this because I know how to use a sewing machine?
Remember when we made aprons as kids?
I wanted to die.
I couldn't figure the sewing machine out.
Well, you're on Team Doofus with me?
Basically, we should all be doing our best to support each other.
Remember what Hana-chan said?
You're the only one who can make the outfit, Gojo.
She's right.
But we might need some help carrying the heavier pieces.
So we'll count on you then.
Right.
Though, if you find you're too busy, it's totally fine to say no.
By the way, where's Mari?
Oh, she's out buying materials.
What?!
You left that up to Mari?!
No way!
We screwed it!
We're not coming back from this!
Okay...
Gojo!
For real though, we're counting on you!
Do your best, dude!
Yeah!
You got it!
Gojo?
What's up?
Kitagawa!
Where are you right now?
Right now?
I'm almost to the station.
Got it!
Wait right there, alright?
I'll go with you!
Hello, Wakuna.
You're pretty chipper today.
Did something happen?
Nope, not at all!
I'm totally the same as usual!
Hmm?
Making a host suit, huh?
For this, I'm thinking of fabric without a pattern, but something with a little bit of glossy finish to it.
It's probably quite similar to a suit, huh?
What's up?
Kitagawa!
Where are you right now?
Right now?
I'm almost to the station.
Got it!
Wait right there, alright?
I'll go with you!
Hello, Wakuna.
You're pretty chipper today.
Did something happen?
Nope, not at all!
I'm totally the same as usual!
Hmm?
Making a host suit, huh?
It's probably quite similar to a suit you'd wear to a party.
In that case, how about this matte satin?
It looks high class, but in an elegant, understated kind of way.
Wow, it's gorgeous!
Wow!
This is seriously on point!
We have a few options here, but I warn you, none of them are cheap.
I've been working my butt off at my job, so we'll be totally fine!
Gotta be that one!
It's just too perfect!
Sure thing!
Oh my gosh!
It has Reisama written all over it!
I think you're right about that!
It's not too fancy, but it's still shiny!
It captures the...
I hope your outfit turns out great!
Outro inter商業 Dury
Outro
笑いない
鏡の中の笑顔の私 昨日とは違う輝いてる
ドキドキしてるこの気持ちは 君に伝えたい電気のハートも
新しい服で 新しい私
心も着替えて
ニュウ ニュウ ニュウ
可愛い界隈
ときめき感じて 君からの変身まで
胸も高鳴る
雨変わるよ 君と変わるよ
可愛い界隈
ニュウ
次回